A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller personal papers, Family and Friends, Series H FA343
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Wines and Spirits, 1951-1971 (Box 58, Folder 604)
- NAR and Mary Todhunter Clark Wedding, June 23, 1930 (Box 59, Folder 605)
- NAR and Mary Todhunter Clark Wedding Gifts, 1930 (Box 59, Folder 606)
- NAR and Mary Todhunter Clark Wedding Gifts, 1930 (Box 59, Folder 607)
- Mary Clark Rockefeller (MCR)
  - General, 1931-1961 (Box 59, Folder 608)
  - Gifts, 1931-1959 (Box 59, Folder 609)
  - Gifts, 1931-1959 (Box 59, Folder 0609A)
  - General, 1931-1971 (Box 59, Folder 610)
  - General, 1931-1971 (Box 59, Folder 0610A)
  - Contributions Correspondence, 1947-1958 (Box 59, Folder 611)
  - Defense Advisory Committee, 1951-1954 (Box 59, Folder 612)
  - Mexico Trip, 1954 (Box 59, Folder 613)
  - Pencoyd Farm, 1956 (Box 60, Folder 614)
  - Pencoyd and Roberts Family Book and Draft (Box 60, Folder 615)
  - Pencoyd and Roberts Family Book Proofs and Correspondence (Box 60, Folder 616)
  - Income Taxes, 1938-1943 (Box 60, Folder 617)
  - Musicale Honoring Mary Clark Rockefeller and NAR, December 17, 1931 (Box 60, Folder 618)
  - Securities, 1931-1956 (Box 60, Folder 619)
  - Finances - Royalty Account (Box 60, Folder 620)
  - Finances - Royalty Account (Box 60, Folder 0620A)
  - Finances - General, 1931-1955 (Box 60, Folder 621)
  - Finances - General, 1931-1955 (Box 60, Folder 0621A)
  - Finances - Venezuelan Oil Royalities (Box 60, Folder 622)
  - Gifts Returned, 1960 (Box 60, Folder 623)
  - MCR and NAR Separation and Divorce, 1961-1962 (Box 60, Folder 625)
  - Separation and Divorce Letters
    - Count of Divorce Letters Received (Box 60, Folder 626)
    - A (Box 61, Folder 627)
    - B (Box 61, Folder 628)
    - C (Box 61, Folder 629)
    - D (Box 61, Folder 630)
    - E-F (Box 61, Folder 631)
    - G (Box 61, Folder 632)
    - H-I (Box 61, Folder 633)
    - J-K (Box 62, Folder 634)
    - L (Box 62, Folder 635)
    - M (Box 62, Folder 636)
    - N-O (Box 62, Folder 637)
    - P (Box 62, Folder 638)
    - R (Box 62, Folder 639)
    - Sa-Si (Box 62, Folder 640)
    - Sk-Sy (Box 63, Folder 641)
    - T (Box 63, Folder 642)
    - V (Box 63, Folder 643)
    - W (Box 63, Folder 644)
    - Y-Z (Box 63, Folder 645)
    - Anonymous (Box 63, Folder 646)
    - Anonymous (Box 63, Folder 647)
    - Foreign Countries (Box 63, Folder 648)
- Margaretta Fitler Rockefeller (MFR)
  - General, 1963-1971 (Box 64, Folder 649)
  - General, 1963-1971 (Box 64, Folder 649a)
  - Staff memos, 1965-1971 (Box 64, Folder 650)
  - Acknowledgments (Box 64, Folder 651)
  - Appeals, A-C (Box 64, Folder 652)
  - Appeals, D-H (Box 64, Folder 653)
  - Appeals, I-M (Box 64, Folder 654)
  - Appeals, N-O (Box 64, Folder 655)
  - Appeals, P-Y (Box 64, Folder 656)
  - Birthday acknowledgments, 1964-1965 (Box 64, Folder 657)
  - Clippings, 1963-1970 (Box 64, Folder 658)
  - Contributions, A-C, 1965-1971 (Box 65, Folder 659)
  - Contributions, D-H, 1965-1971 (Box 65, Folder 660)
  - Contributions, I-L, 1965-1971 (Box 65, Folder 661)
  - Contributions, M-O, 1965-1971 (Box 65, Folder 662)
  - Contributions, P-S, 1965-1971 (Box 65, Folder 663)
  - Contributions, U-Y, 1965-1971 (Box 65, Folder 664)
  - Contributions overall, 1967-1971 (Box 65, Folder 665)
  - Contributions, small gifts, 1963-1967 (Box 65, Folder 666)
  - Dinner dance thank-yous, June 1967 (Box 66, Folder 668)
  - Federation of Women's Republican Clubs, 1964-1965 (Box 66, Folder 669)
  - Financial investments, 1968-1971 (Box 66, Folder 670)
  - Gifts returned and accepted, 1964-1970 (Box 66, Folder 671)
  - Goddard Gaities, 1964-1965 (Box 66, Folder 672)
  - IBEC holdings, 1965-1970 (Box 66, Folder 673)
  - Invitations to serve, A-K, 1964-1971 (Box 66, Folder 674)
  - Invitations to serve, L-Y, 1964-1971 (Box 66, Folder 675)
  - [Closed Folder] (Box 66, Folder 667)
  - Memberships, 1967 (Box 66, Folder 676)
  - Miscellaneous, A-Z, 1966-1971 (Box 66, Folder 677)
  - Northern Student Movement, 1964 (Box 67, Folder 679)
  - Heather Peter mail, 1964-1967 (Box 67, Folder 680)
  - Friends of Channel 13, 1971 (Box 67, Folder 682)
  - Governor's Club, 1966-1970 (Box 67, Folder 683)
  - League of Women Voters of the Tarrytowns, 1963-1972 (Box 67, Folder 684)
  - Publicity and press requests, 1964-1971 (Box 67, Folder 685)
  - Purchases, 1965-1969 (Box 67, Folder 686)
  - Shipley School, 1963-1971 (Box 67, Folder 687)
  - Society of Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1967 (Box 67, Folder 688)
  - [Closed Folder] (Box 67, Folder 678)
  - Latin American presidential mission trip, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 689)
  - Trips, Virginia and West Virginia, September 1963 (Box 67, Folder 690)
  - Trips, Rockford, Illinois, September 1963 (Box 67, Folder 691)
  - Trips, Europe, September-October 1963 (Box 67, Folder 692)
  - Trips, New Hampshire, October 1963 (Box 68, Folder 693)
  - [Closed Folder] (Box 67, Folder 681)
  - Trips, Utah and California, October 1963 (Box 68, Folder 694)
  - Trips, New Hampshire, January 1964 (Box 68, Folder 695)
  - Trips, California, January 1964 (Box 68, Folder 696)
  - Trips, Oregon, February 1964 (Box 68, Folder 697)
  - Trips, New Hampshire, March 1964 (Box 68, Folder 698)
  - Trips, Spain, November 1964 (Box 68, Folder 699)
  - Trips, proposed, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 700)
  - Who's Who of American Women, 1970 (Box 68, Folder 701)
  - Contributions, 1964 (Box 68, Folder 702)
  - Contributions, 1965 (Box 68, Folder 703)
  - Contributions, 1966 (Box 68, Folder 704)
  - Contributions, 1967 (Box 68, Folder 705)
  - Contributions, 1968 (Box 68, Folder 706)
  - Contributions, 1968 (Box 68, Folder 707)
  - Contributions, 1969-1970 (Box 69, Folder 708)
  - Contributions, 1970-1971 (Box 69, Folder 709)
  - Contribution appeals, no answer, 1967-1969 (Box 69, Folder 710)
  - Contribution appeals, no answer, 1970-1971 (Box 69, Folder 711)
  - Reports of contributions, 1963-1971 (Box 69, Folder 712)
  - Political contributions, 1964-1966 (Box 69, Folder 713)
  - Political contributions, 1967 (Box 69, Folder 714)
  - Political contributions, 1968 (Box 70, Folder 715)
  - Political contributions, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 716)
  - Political contributions, 1970 (Box 70, Folder 717)
  - Official invitations accepted, 1964-1965 (Box 70, Folder 718)
  - Correspondence on official acceptances, 1966-1971 (Box 70, Folder 719)
  - Official acceptances for recipes, 1963-1965 (Box 70, Folder 720)
  - Official acceptances, 1967 (Box 70, Folder 721)
  - Official acceptances, 1968 (Box 70, Folder 722)
  - Official acceptances, 1969-1971 (Box 70, Folder 723)
  - Official regrets, 1965 (Box 71, Folder 724)
  - Official regrets, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 725)
  - Official regrets, 1968-1971 (Box 71, Folder 726)
  - Official regrets, 1968-1971 (Box 71, Folder 727)
  - Letters of thanks, 1964, 1968-1971 (Box 71, Folder 728)
  - Thank-you correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 71, Folder 729)
  - Thank-you correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 71, Folder 730)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1968-1971 (Box 71, Folder 731)
  - Correspondence with John Lomenzo (Box 71, Folder 732)
  - Correspondence on gifts for Bartols, 1963-1972 (Box 71, Folder 733)
  - National Governors' Conference, 1963-1969 (Box 72, Folder 734)
  - Republican Governors' Conference, December 1967 (Box 72, Folder 735)
  - Republican Governors' Conference, December 1968 (Box 72, Folder 736)
  - Republican National Conventions, 1964, 1968 (Box 72, Folder 737)
  - Republican Women for Nixon-Agnew, 1968 (Box 72, Folder 738)
  - Women's National Republican Club, 1963-1968 (Box 72, Folder 739)
  - Republican State Women's Finance Committee, 1966 (Box 72, Folder 740)
  - Correspondence, A-B, 1963-1966 (Box 72, Folder 741)
  - Correspondence, C, 1963-1966 (Box 72, Folder 742)
  - Correspondence, D-E, 1963-1966 (Box 72, Folder 743)
  - Correspondence, F-G, 1963-1966 (Box 72, Folder 744)
  - Correspondence, H-K, 1963-1966 (Box 73, Folder 745)
  - Correspondence, L, 1963-1966 (Box 73, Folder 746)
  - Correspondence, M, 1963-1966 (Box 73, Folder 747)
  - Correspondence, Executive Mansion, 1963-1966 (Box 73, Folder 748)
  - Correspondence, M-P, 1963-1966 (Box 73, Folder 749)
  - Correspondence, R, 1963-1966 (Box 73, Folder 750)
  - Correspondence, S-T, 1963-1966 (Box 73, Folder 751)
  - Correspondence, U-Y, 1963-1966 (Box 73, Folder 752)
  - Personal correspondence, 1965 (Box 73, Folder 753)
  - Personal correspondence, A-D, 1967 (Box 74, Folder 754)
  - Personal correspondence, F-I, 1967 (Box 74, Folder 755)
  - Personal correspondence, K-N, 1967 (Box 74, Folder 756)
  - Personal correspondence, P-S, 1967 (Box 74, Folder 757)
  - Personal correspondence, Saratoga Performing Arts Center, 1967 (Box 74, Folder 758)
  - Personal correspondence, T-Y, 1967 (Box 74, Folder 759)
  - Appointment calendar, 1967 (Box 74, Folder 760)
  - Appointment calendar, 1968 (Box 74, Folder 761)
  - Appointment calendar, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 762)
  - Appointment calendar, 1970 (Box 74, Folder 763)
  - Appointment calendar, 1971 (Box 74, Folder 764)
  - Personal correspondence, A-B, 1968 (Box 75, Folder 765)
  - Personal correspondence, C, 1968 (Box 75, Folder 766)
  - Personal correspondence, D-F, 1968 (Box 75, Folder 767)
  - Personal correspondence, G-K, 1968 (Box 75, Folder 768)
  - Personal correspondence, L-M, 1968 (Box 75, Folder 769)
  - Personal correspondence, N-P, 1968 (Box 75, Folder 770)
  - Personal correspondence, R-S, 1968 (Box 75, Folder 771)
  - Personal correspondence, T-Y, 1968 (Box 75, Folder 772)
  - Wedding congratulations, A (Box 76, Folder 773)
  - Wedding congratulations, B (Box 76, Folder 774)
  - Wedding congratulations, C (Box 76, Folder 775)
  - Wedding congratulations, D (Box 76, Folder 776)
  - Wedding congratulations, E (Box 76, Folder 777)
  - Wedding congratulations, F (Box 76, Folder 778)
  - Wedding congratulations, G (Box 76, Folder 779)
  - Wedding congratulations, H (Box 77, Folder 780)
  - Wedding congratulations, I (Box 77, Folder 781)
  - Wedding congratulations, J (Box 77, Folder 782)
  - Wedding congratulations, K (Box 77, Folder 783)
  - Wedding congratulations, L (Box 77, Folder 784)
  - Wedding congratulations, Ma (Box 77, Folder 785)
  - Wedding congratulations, Mc-Mu (Box 77, Folder 786)
  - Wedding congratulations, N (Box 77, Folder 787)
  - Wedding congratulations, O (Box 77, Folder 788)
  - Wedding congratulations, P-Q (Box 77, Folder 789)
  - Wedding congratulations, R (Box 78, Folder 790)
  - Wedding congratulations, Sa-Sh (Box 78, Folder 791)
  - Wedding congratulations, Si-Sv (Box 78, Folder 792)
  - Wedding congratulations, T (Box 78, Folder 793)
  - Wedding congratulations, U-V (Box 78, Folder 794)
  - Wedding congratulations, W (Box 78, Folder 795)
  - Wedding congratulations, Y-Z (Box 78, Folder 796)
  - Wedding congratulations, foreign A-J (Box 78, Folder 797)
  - Wedding congratulations, foreign K-Z (Box 78, Folder 798)
  - Wedding, political comments, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 799)
  - Wedding, appreciation letters, May 1963 (Box 79, Folder 800)
  - Wedding, cables to family, May 1963 (Box 79, Folder 801)
  - Wedding, thank yous, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 802)
  - Wedding, handwritten thank yous, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 803)
  - Wedding gifts, accepted, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 804)
  - Wedding gifts, returned, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 805)
  - Anniversary thank yous, 1964-1967 (Box 79, Folder 806)
  - Wedding clippings, May 5, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 807)
  - Wedding clippings, May 6, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 808)
  - Wedding clippings, May 7, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 809)
  - Wedding clippings, May 8, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 810)
  - Wedding clippings, May 9, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 811)
  - Wedding clippings, May 10, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 812)
  - Wedding clippings, May 12-July 1963 (Box 79, Folder 813)
  - Wedding clippings, miscellaneous, May 1963 (Box 79, Folder 814)
  - Wedding clippings, May 1963 (Box 80, Folder 815)
  - Wedding clippings, May 1963 (Box 80, Folder 816)
  - Wedding and honeymoon clippings, May 1963 (Box 80, Folder 817)
  - Honeymoon clippings, May 1963 (Box 80, Folder 818)
  - Wedding crank letters (1), 1963 (Box 80, Folder 819)
  - Wedding crank letters (2), 1963 (Box 80, Folder 820)
  - Wedding crank letters (3), 1963 (Box 80, Folder 821)
  - Wedding crank letters (4), 1963 (Box 80, Folder 822)
  - Wedding crank letters (5), 1963 (Box 80, Folder 823)
  - Wedding crank letters (6), 1963 (Box 81, Folder 824)
  - Wedding crank letters (7), 1963 (Box 81, Folder 825)
  - Wedding crank letters (8), 1963 (Box 81, Folder 826)
  - Wedding crank letters (9), 1963 (Box 81, Folder 827)
  - Wedding crank letters (10), 1963 (Box 81, Folder 828)
  - Wedding crank letters (11), 1963 (Box 81, Folder 829)
  - Wedding crank letters (12), 1963 (Box 81, Folder 830)
  - Wedding crank letters (13), 1963 (Box 81, Folder 831)
  - Wedding crank letters (14), 1963 (Box 82, Folder 832)
  - Wedding crank letters (15), 1963 (Box 82, Folder 833)
- Rodman C. Rockefeller (RCR)
  - General, 1932-1949 (Box 84, Folder 852)
  - General, 1950-1959 (Box 84, Folder 853)
  - General, 1960-1967 (Box 85, Folder 854)
  - NAR Letters to Rodman, 1947-1953 (Box 85, Folder 855)
  - NAR Letters with Rodman, 1954-1956 (Box 85, Folder 856)
  - Rodman and Barbara Rockefeller, 1953-1971 (Box 85, Folder 857)
  - Rodman and Barbara Rockefeller, 1953-1971 (Box 85, Folder 0857A)
  - Family Correspondence, 1933-1958 (Box 85, Folder 858)
  - Family Correspondence, 1933-1958 (Box 85, Folder 0858A)
  - Contributions, 1955-1962 (Box 85, Folder 859)
  - Correspondence with John D. Rockefeller Jr., 1932-1960 (Box 85, Folder 860)
  - Chilean Order of Merit, 1964 (Box 85, Folder 861)
  - Dartmouth College, 1950-1953 (Box 85, Folder 862)
  - Wedding to Barbara Olsen, June 17, 1953 (Box 86, Folder 863)
  - Office, 1955-1971 (Box 86, Folder 864)
  - Trip to Europe and Visit with Ann Rockefeller, 1951 (Box 86, Folder 865)
  - Trip to Europe and Visit with Ann Rockefeller, 1951 (Box 86, Folder 0865A)
  - Trip to Honduras, 1948 (Box 86, Folder 866)
  - Trip to Venezuela, 1949 (Box 86, Folder 867)
  - Trip to Peru, Summer 1952 (Box 86, Folder 868)
- Martha Baird Rockefeller
  - Estate Matters (Box 129, Folder 1221)
  - Estate Matters (Box 129, Folder 1221A)
  - Estate and Appraisal (Box 129, Folder 1222)
  - Estate and Appraisal (Box 129, Folder 1222A)
  - Estate Price-Value List (Box 129, Folder 1223)